https://www.coastpneumatics.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
$0.00
0
(888) 918-8432
ProductsMenu ToggleDirectional Control ValvesMenu Toggle2 Way Solenoid Valves3 Way Solenoid Valves4 Way Solenoid ValvesAir Operated ValvesMechanical & Hand Operated ValvesQuick Exhaust ValvesFlow ControlsRelief ValveAirline EquipmentMenu ToggleAir RegulatorsCombination UnitsFiltersSoft Start ValvesShut-Off ValvesSilencers & MufflersLubricatorsConnectorsMenu ToggleAir FittingsBrass ConnectorsConduit FittingsHose Barb ConnectorsQuick Connect CouplingsQuick Release CouplingsTubingMenu TogglePolyethylene TubingPolyurethane TubingTube CuttersCylinders & ActuatorsMenu TogglePneumatic CylindersPiston CylindersGuided CylindersElectric ActuatorsGrippersDial Pressure GaugesMenu ToggleGeneral Purpose GaugeStainless Steel GaugeBrass Case Liquid Filled GaugeGeneral Purpose Liquid Filled GaugePrecision Test Pressure GaugeVacuum Diaphragm GaugeSensors & SwitchesMenu TogglePressure SwitchVacuum SwitchElectricalBrandsMenu ToggleResourcesMenu ToggleSCFM ConversionAirflow Unit ConversionCylinder SizingIndustriesAbout UsContact Us
General Information
We thank you for joining the Coast Pneumatics community. This privacy policy covers CoastPneumatics.com and all of its subdomains. We take your privacy very seriously. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please reach out to us by phone: 888-313-5609 or email: sales@coastpneumatics.com
What information do we collect?
You can access and browse our website without providing any personal information. However in the event you would like to register on our site for the purpose of receiving order updates, tracking orders, entering a contest, downloading material, or to receive marketing material we may ask for information that might personally identify you. This information may include your full name, company name, phone number, email address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, referring url’s, country, and location. This information is primarily needed for the security maintenance and operation of our websites, and for our internal reporting and analytics purposes.
How do we use your information?
We use the information we receive or collect for the following:
To allow you to create an account or login to an existing account.
To provide you with marketing and promotional materials.
To advise you of our products, services, or changes in our terms & conditions.
To process, manage, track or update your orders.
To provide advertising and display content tailored to your interest and/or location and (work with third parties to deliver such content) to measure its effectiveness.
To request your feedback
To evaluate the effectiveness of our promotional and marketing campaigns, identify user trends, and to improve our sites, products, and overall user experience.
Will your information be shared with anyone?
Coast Pneumatics, Inc. does not sell, rent, or gives away information that will personally identify customers to third parties except when such information is required by third-party service providers for legitimate business purposes. Third-party services may include payment processing, email delivery, hosting services, marketing, and analytics.
Cookies and tracking technologies
Cookies are small files which are stored on a user’s computer. They are designed to hold a modest amount of data specific to a particular user such as preferred language and location. Web pages within our website may include cookies to provide you with the best possible user experience.
Coastpneumatics.com uses cookies for the following reasons:
Provide you with the best possible and most personalized user experience.
Recognizing your settings and preferences when you sign into your account.
Analyze and track interactions with coastpneumatics.com
Different browsers offer different ways to manage, or delete cookies.
You can opt out of the use of cookies by visiting the links below:
Google Ad Settings http://www.google.com/settings/ads
Other third parties: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
Information Retention
Your information is kept for as long as it is necessary for the purposes detailed in this privacy policy. We do not retain your information longer than 6 months past the termination of the user’s account. Once we deem we have no requirement of your information for a legitimate business purpose we will anonymize, and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.
Policy Changes and Updates
Coast Pneumatics reserves the right to change or update this policy at any time we deem necessary to maintain compliance with relevant laws. Current version of our Privacy Policy will be posted on our website www.coastpneumatics.com. If user continues to use our site after we change this Privacy Policy, then user accepts all changes.
Do we collect information from minors?
Coast Pneumatics does not knowingly solicit or collect data from or market to minors under the age of 18.
How do we keep your information safe?
Coast Pneumatics has implemented appropriate technical and organizational security measures designed to protect the security of any information we have under our control. Nonetheless, you are ultimately responsible for maintaining confidentiality of your login and password. Although, we do our best to protect your information all transmission of personal information to and from our site is at your own risk. It is recommended you access our services within a safe and secure network.
If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you can reach us by calling 888-313-5609 or by post to:
Coast Pneumatics, Inc.
8055 E. Crystal Dr.
Anaheim, Ca. 92807
United States
Coast Pneumatics
Brands
Air LogicFestoLinkTechMem-coNoShokPeterPaul Back
Products
Connectors
Air FittingsBrass ConnectorsConduit FittingsHose Barb Connectors Back
Directional Control Valves
2 Way Solenoid Valves3 Way Solenoid Valves4 Way Solenoid ValvesCheck ValvesAir Operated ValvesMechanical & Hand Operated ValvesQuick Exhaust ValvesFlow ControlsRelief Valve Back
Dial Indicating Pressure Gauges
Subminiature Pressure GaugesGeneral Purpose GaugeStainless Steel GaugeBrass Case Liquid Filled GaugeGeneral Purpose Liquid Filled GaugePrecision Test Pressure GaugeVacuum Diaphragm Gauge Back
Airline Equipment
Shut-Off ValvesAir RegulatorsFiltersLubricatorsSoft Start ValvesSilencers & Exhaust Mufflers Back
Back
SCFM ConversionContact UsRequest a QuoteCartCheckout
